

Shruti Naoley

Pune, Maharashtra9096964621

☑ naoleyshruti@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/shruti-naoley/

Objective

Seeking a position to utilize my skills and abilities for the growth of the organization that offers professional rise while being resourceful, innovative and flexible.

Summary

Highly motivated, deadline-committed, goal-driven accountant with over 6.5 years of experience in the IT industry. Digital marketing certified with proven success in implementing the marketing strategy and the creation and execution of outbound campaigns. Exceptional communication and presentation skills. Diligently work with the team and increase the growth of the business.

Expertise in tools:

- SEMrush
- Pardot
- Salesforce
- HubSpot
- LinkedIn Sales Navigator
- · Zoom Info
- Google Analytics
- Google Search Console

Professional Experience

Manager- Marketing

Sept 2019 - Present

Hurix Digital

- Managing social media presence ensuring high levels of web traffic, customer engagement and conversion
- Working on social media (LinkedIn, Twitter) content and maintaining social calendars
- Interacting with the generated leads and qualifying them for the sales team to get MQL
- Coordinating with accounts, stakeholders and vendors
- Managing events and incharge of all event activities and promotions
- Expert in the SEO activities including keyword research and optimization, content writing, increasing organic traffic and Wordpress uploading
- Managing the overall email marketing campaigns along with knowledge of campaign creation and tracking, deliverability, lead scoring, domain checking
- Marketing automation and email workflows management create update, and manage the email campaign calendar Salesforce / CRM opportunities, and contacts management
- Hands on knowledge of MS office, Word, PowerPoint and Excel
- Positive attitude, team player and able to figure out solutions experience of working with sales team
- · Qualifying the inbound and outbound leads and creating an opportunity for the sales team

Marketing Executive

Mar 2018 - Aug 2019

WhiteHedge Technologies/ CloudHedge

- Drafting personalized mailers and content writing for the blogs on new emerging technologies
- Initiating various email campaigns to generate leads
- Targeting SMEs and large enterprises in USA, UK and India
- Setting up the meetings and presenting the services/solutions/platforms to the prospects to get MQL
- Connecting to the clients via social media platforms mainly via LinkedIn and Twitter
- Collecting database of accounts and executing the email campaigns to generate leads
- Cold Calling and follow-up calls
- Demand generation and the strategies to generate leads

Marketing Intern (MBA Projects/Internship)

May 2016 - Aug 2016

Mercedes Benz B.U. Bhandari

- Event Management for Mercedes-Benz AMG performance Tour
- Event Management of GLC star off-road adventure event for newly launched vehicle
- Project on the automobile industry
- Invitation Calling to customer /Cold calling
- Lead generation
- Social media analysis of competitors
- Created SMS blast script for offer

Academic Qualification

Sr. No	Name of Examination	Board / University	Year
1	MBA (Marketing)	University of Pune	2017
2	B.B.A (Marketing)	University of Pune	2015
3	H.S.C (10+2)	State Board, Maharashtra	2011
4	S.S.C (10th)	State Board, Maharashtra	2009

Personal Details:

 Name : Shruti Naoley

DOB : 4th Sep 1992
Language Known : English, Marathi, Hindi
Temporary Address : Tathawade, Pune, India

Declaration

I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Shruti Naoley

